Third Training Grounds
（ナルト）いくぜ
Let's go!
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
影分身かげぶんしんの術
Not bad.
（はたけカカシ）やるなあ
Nice... Since he's trapped in midair...
（春野はるのサクラ）うまい！
身動きの取れない
空中での移動手段に
he used the Shadow Clone Jutsu
as a means for movement.
影分身を利用した
Transform!
（ナルト）んぐっ
ううっ
うっ…
Okay, that's as far as you go.
（カカシ）はい そこまで
（カカシ）身長 だいぶ伸びたな
He's gotten pretty tall.
And not only that...
おまけに…
（ナルト）フッ ヘヘ…
His timing for using
the Shadow Clone Jutsu has gotten better.
（カカシ）影分身の使い方
タイミング うまくなっちゃって
Oho...
（自来也じらいや）ほお～
Not bad.
（綱手つなで）やるなあ
That's incredible.
（シズネ）すごい
（カカシ）成長したな ナルト
You've grown, haven't you, Naruto?
However...
だが…
Well, it seems you're just
as impatient as ever.
まっ せっかちなのは
相変わらず
変わってないみたいだな
I haven't even said start yet,
have I?
まだスタートは言ってないだろ？
（カカシ）そう慌てんなよ
Don't be so hasty.
I haven't even said start yet, have I?
まだ スタートとは言ってないだろ？
Now then, let's begin.
じゃあ 始めるぞ
Ready...start!
（カカシ）よ～い
スタート
（サクラ）あっ
（ナルト）うっ
♪～
～♪
（カカシ）じゃあ 始めるぞ
Now then, let's begin!
よ～い
Ready...start!
スタート
（サクラ）あっ
（ナルト）うっ
クソ～
Damn it!
やられたってばよ
I've been had!
（サクラ）もう～ ナルトのドジ！
Come on, Naruto, you goof!
The Results of Training
（サソリ）ご苦労
Good work...
Do you remember me?
俺のこと思い出してくれた？
（由良ゆうら）あ…
もちろんです サソリ様
Of course, I do, Lord Sasori.
（デイダラ）そりゃ そうだ
Of course, he does.
忘れてたら
術になんねえだろ？ うん
It wouldn't be much of
a Jutsu if he didn't.
（サソリ）記憶が戻れば
忠実な部下だぜ
They become loyal subordinates
after regaining their memory.
（デイダラ）そろそろ いいか？
I say it's about ready?
よし できたぞ うん
All right, it's done...
（デイダラ）サソリの旦那は
ここで見てればいい うん
Sasori, my good man.
You watch from here...
Okay.
里へは…
I'll attack the village...
from above.
上から攻める
どうだい 旦那
この芸術的造形は？ うん
What do you think of
this artistic form...?
（サソリ）あんまり
待たせんなよ デイダラ
Don't make me wait too long, Deidara!
（デイダラ）ヘッ…
（デイダラ）一尾(いちび) 守鶴(しゅかく)の人柱力(じんちゅうりき)
砂漠の我愛羅(があら)か うん
One-Tail, the Jinchuriki of Shukaku,
Gaara of the desert, eh?
さて どんなものか
Now then, I wonder what he's like.
（綱手）さあ どうする？ サクラ
Now...
What're you going to do, Sakura?
（サクラ）右
Right? Above? Left?
上
左
Behind?
後ろ
どこでもないなら…
If he's in none of those places...
（サクラ）下！
He must be below.
（ナルト）あ～ とっ とっ…
（ナルト）ええ…
Huh?
（カカシ）な…
なんつうバカ力だ
Wh-What ridiculous strength.
よし 上出来だ
All right, well done.
（カカシ）五代目～
Fifth Hokage...
サクラに教えたの
医療忍術だけじゃないのね
You didn't just teach Sakura
Medical Ninjutsu, huh?
（自来也）あのキレ具合と あの怪力
That short temper and
incredible strength.
見事な綱手２号を育てやがったのォ
She raised a splendid second Tsunade.
Kakashi Sensei.
（サクラ）カカシ先生
（カカシ）ん？
Huh?
見～つけた
I found you.
（ナルト）サ…
サクラちゃんの前でバカするの
I'd...I'd better stop acting like
an idiot in front of Sakura.
もう やめよ
I'll get killed...!
殺される
（カカシ）最大チャクラを
一気に体内で練り上げ
She built up her maximum
Chakra inside her body at once
瞬時に拳に全集中
and instantly concentrated
all of it into her fist.
相当なチャクラコントロールが
なけりゃ できない芸当だ
That's a feat that can't be done
without considerable Chakra control.
医療忍術に怪力か
Medical Ninjutsu along
with superhuman strength...
いや それだけじゃない
No. It's more than that.
サクラは 本来
幻術げんじゅつタイプだからな
Sakura's originally a Genjutsu-type,
after all.
She might just become
a better Kunoichi than the Fifth Hokage.
こりゃ 五代目以上の
くノ一になるかもね
（カカシ）よ～し 今度は
俺のほうからもいきますか
All right, now I guess
it's my turn, huh?
One.
Two.
Three.
上空の見張りが３人か うん
So there are three people
guarding the skies...
しかし なかなか芸術的なデザイン
してやがんじゃねえか この里
Still, this village sure has
quite the artistic design to it.
まさに 壊しがいが
あるってもんだが うん
It's certainly worth destroying, though...
（デイダラ）ここは 隠密行動だな
It's time for covert action from here on.
（カカシ）いる いる
There he is.
忍たるもの 基本は
気配を消し隠れるべし
The basics for a Shinobi are
to eliminate their presence
and remain hidden.
あのころとは大違いだな
This is totally different from
back then.
（カカシ）忍たるもの 基本は
気配を消し隠れるべし
The basics for a Shinobi
are to eliminate their presence
and remain hidden.
All right, everyone seems
to be well hidden...
（カカシ）よ～し
みんな うまく隠れ…
（カカシ）ん？
あっ いざ 尋常に勝負 勝負～
Now, fight me fair and square!
Say, aren't you just a little bit off there?
（カカシ）あのさあ
お前 ちとズレてない？
（カカシ）おっと
（ナルト）うっ うわ～
（カカシ）２人とも 教えてやる
Let me teach the two of you something.
忍戦術しのびせんじゅつの心得 その１
Shinobi Battle Skills, part one...Taijutsu.
体術たいじゅつ
隙あり！
You're wide open!
If I can hit him once...
（サクラ）１発 当たれば
It won't mean a thing
if you don't hit me.
（カカシ）当たらなければ
どうということはない
（カカシ）おっ
Phew, that was a close one.
うへ～ 危ない 危ない
影分身の術
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
（カカシ）ん？
（ナルト）いくぞ
Here I come!
All right, bring it on.
（カカシ）よ～し こい！
もらった！
The bell's mine.
（カカシ）ぬわ～
（ナルト）うわっ
You won't get away!
逃がすか！
えっ？ 影舞葉かげぶよう
Dancing Leaf Shadow...?!
あっ
これってば ゲジマユの！
This is Bushy Brow's...!
カカシ先生のコピー忍術
It's Kakashi Sensei's Copy Ninjutsu!
（ナルト）うわっ うわあ～！
（カカシ）さあ 本体はどこだ？
Now...where's the real one?
（ナルト）ここだってばよ
Right here.
（カカシ）うっ
（ナルト）秘伝 体術奥義たいじゅつおうぎ
Secret Finger Jutsu.
（カカシ）ぬおっ おお…
（ナルト）千年殺せんねんごろし
A Thousand Years of Death!
（カカシ）どわ～
Now...where's the real one?
（カカシ）さあ 本体はどこだ？
（ナルト）ここだってばよ
Right here!
（カカシ）うっ
（ナルト）秘伝 体術奥義
Secret Finger Jutsu!
（カカシ）ぬおっ おお…
（ナルト）千年殺し
A Thousand Years of Death!
（カカシ）どわ～
（ナルト）うっ クソ～
外したってばよ
Damn it. I missed!
That was a close one...
In a different sense.
（カカシ）今のは危なかったぞ
別の意味で
（サクラ）とりゃあ～
（カカシ）あ…
ふ～
It used to be so easy.
（カカシ）昔は楽だったのになあ
I'll tear you apart!
（ナルト）ボッコボコにしてやる～！
クソ～
Damn it! You can't dodge this!
今度 足蹴り
あっ クソ～ もう！
Geez, man!
Huh?
あれっ？
Ninja don't let their opponent
get behind them over and over, you idiot!
（カカシ）忍者が何べんも
後ろ取られんな バカ
Leaf Village Secret Finger Jutsu!
（カカシ）木ノ葉隠このはがくれれ秘伝 体術奥義
あっ
（刺す音）
（ナルト）うっ
（カカシ）千年殺し！
（ナルト）うぎゃ～
A Thousand Years of Death!
She's over there, huh?
（カカシ）あそこか
（カカシ）フッ
（サクラ）サスケ君
どこにいるのかな
Sasuke, where are you?
Don't tell me Sensei
already got to you!
まさか もう先生に…
No, that'd never happen to him!
いや サスケ君に限って
そんなことないわよね
（物音）
（サクラ）あっ！
（サクラ）セーフ
気づかれてない！
I'm safe! He hasn't noticed me!
Sakura, behind you.
（カカシ）サクラ 後ろ
えっ？
うわあ～！
They've been apart for two years,
（カカシ）長いこと
離れていたというのに
and yet his teamwork with Sakura
isn't that bad.
サクラとの
コンビネーションも悪くない
新刊の続きが
気になるところではあるが
Though I want to...
find out what happens next
in the new volume...
多重影分身たじゅうかげぶんしんの術！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
As always, the sheer number
of his clones amazes me...
（カカシ）相変わらず
この数には圧倒される
（ナルト）いくぞ！
（ナルトたち）お～！
Let's go!
- Yeah!
うわあ～！
（サクラ）とや～！
Good grief... It looks like
I won't have time for reading.
（カカシ）や～れ やれ
読書してる暇は なさそうだな
おもしろくなってきたのォ
Things are getting interesting.
やりますねえ ナルト君とサクラ
Naruto and Sakura
are pretty good, aren't they?
まだまだ これからだよ
Things are just getting started.
Now then, what should I do...?
（カカシ）さて どうするか
（デイダラ）フフッ
Wh-What's this strange thing?!
（砂すなの里さとの忍）おっ
なんだ この変なのは
ああっ
It's not  strange, you know.
変なのはねえだろ
（砂の里の忍）ん？ おおっ
（砂の里の忍）うう…
Sure enough, fools don't understand
what art is all about...
やっぱ バカは芸術ってもんが
分かってねえな うん
（砂の里の忍）うう…
I'll show you with your own bodies.
（デイダラ）体で教えてやるよ
True art...is an explosion!
芸術は 爆発だ！
I'm sure I heard the sound
of the bells from this way.
確かに こっちのほうから
聞こえたんだ 鈴の音
There's a possibility that
he rang them on purpose.
わざと聞かせた可能性もあるわ
Be careful.
気をつけて
Yeah, it's Kakashi Sensei, after all.
ああ カカシ先生だからな
（ナルト）ん…
（サクラ）あ…
（サスケ）うっ ああ…
Sasuke!
サスケ…
サスケ君
Sasuke.
（サスケ）う… ナルト…
Naruto, Sakura... Help me.
サクラ…
助けてくれ…
I got away from Orochimaru.
大蛇丸おろちまる… ところから…
逃げてきたんだ
助けてくれ
Help me.
ナルト サクラ…
Naruto, Sakura... Please.
頼む…
It's too bad... I want to talk with Sasuke
a little while longer, but...
残念だわ サスケ君とは
もうしばらく お話していたいけど
（サスケ）うっ うう…
Release!
解かい！
I'm not interested in illusions,
you see.
幻には興味ないのよね
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
影分身の術
Naruto, Kakashi Sensei's behind
that tree there.
（サクラ）ナルト
そこの木の後ろにカカシ先生
Oh, no!
（カカシ）しまった！
Yeah, I know.
ああ 分かってるってばよ！
Rasengan!
螺旋丸らせんがん！
Kakashi Sensei.
カカシ先生
Huh?
（カカシ）ん？
なんか言うことあるでしょ？
前は 私
聞きそびれちゃったけど
（カカシ）忍戦術 その２
幻術げんじゅつ
えっ？
今の何？
ええ？ ちょっと 先生は？
えっ？ ええ？ どうなってんの？
ええ～ 何が何？
（サスケ）サクラ…
（サクラ）サスケ君？
た… 助けて… くれ…
（サクラ）あ…
うわあ～！
（カカシ）あのときは 簡単に
引っかかってくれちゃったのになあ
カカシ先生 芸 なさすぎ
同じ手に 何度も
引っかかるわけないでしょ
そうだ そうだ
（カカシ）いいや
そうともかぎらないぞ
やりぃ！ 鈴が落ちたってばよ！
ナルト ダメ！
（ナルト）いただき～！
うわっ ああっ！
（カカシ）ほ～ら
ナルトなら 前と同じ手に…
ん？
（ナルト）んなもん
引っかかるわけねえってばよ！
なっ…
変わり身の術
（ナルト）クッソ～
（サクラ）バカ！
だから言ったじゃないの！
（カカシ）やっぱ
もう同じ手は通用しないか
潜入成功
（我愛羅があら）そこまでだ
ほう…
♪～
～♪
見えますでしょうか
ものすごい爆煙です
砂隠れの里の上空で 壮絶な
乱気流が巻き起こっております
詳しく分かりますか？
はい 風影かぜかげ様と侵入者が 空中で
激しい戦いを繰り広げているもようです
住民たちは 戦いを見守るしかなく…
ああ～！
大丈夫ですか？
（せきばらい）
音声が途切れたようです
引き続き 情報が入りしだい
お伝えします
次回「砂の人柱力」
（綱手）暁(あかつき)は みずから里を捨て
出ていった忍たちにより
共通の目的を達成するため構成された
謎の組織である
黒い衣 赤い雲模様の装束を身にまとい
裏の世界で暗躍し
かつては あの大蛇丸も
所属していたという情報もある
現在までに木ノ葉と接触したのは
うちは一族を滅亡させた
サスケの実の兄
万華鏡写輪眼まんげきょうしゃりんがんを持つ
うちはイタチ
そして
元 霧隠きりがくれの怪人
干柿ほしがき鬼鮫きさめの２名
第１の接触では木ノ葉が誇る上忍じょうにん
カカシ アスマ 紅くれないですら
手も足も出ないという完敗を喫した
彼らの目的は
ナルトの九尾きゅうびを手に入れること
その使用目的は
いまだ解明されていない
引き続き調査を要する